Beauty from Pain is a romance, drama film directed by Christine Luby.
After a devastating heartbreak, an aspiring musician escapes to Australia.
She agrees to a no-strings romance with a billionaire winemaker, but when she falls in
love she must choose to walk away or risk her heart on a man afraid to love.
Laurelyn Prescott, played by Samantha Allsop.
Jack Henry, played by Jackson Gallagher.
Addison Donovan, played by Arielle Cartwright.
Zac, played by Callan Colley.
Audrey Bagshaw, played by Brittany Grey.
Persephone, played by Jasmine Barui.
A Real Pain is a 2024 comedy-drama film written and directed by Jesse Eisenberg.
An international co-production between Poland and the United States, the film stars Eisenberg and Kieran Culkin as mismatched cousins who reunite for a Jewish
heritage tour through Poland in honor of their late grandmother, but tensions between them surface amidst the backdrop of their family history.
Its supporting cast includes Will Sharpe, Jennifer Grey, Kurt
Egyiawan, Liza Sadovy, and Daniel Oreskes.
Principal photography took place primarily in Poland from May to June 2023.
A Real Pain premiered at the 2024 Sundance Film Festival, where it won the Waldo Salt Screenwriting Award, and was released
theatrically in the United States on November 1, 2024, and in Poland on November 8 by Searchlight Pictures.
The film grossed $24.9 million worldwide.
A Real Pain was critically acclaimed and received several accolades, including two nominations at the 97th Academy Awards and 78th British Academy Film Awards, and four at the 82nd Golden
Globe Awards; Culkin won the Oscar, BAFTA, SAG, Golden Globe and Critics' Choice for Best Supporting Actor, while Eisenberg won the BAFTA Award for Best Original Screenplay.
It was named as one of the top ten films of 2024 by the American
Film Institute and the National Board of Review.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
heartbreak, romantic drama, winemaking.
The tone is emotional.